George W. Henry Foundation and the Canon Clinton Jones Archive 1933-1986 (bulk 1963-1986) GLBTQ.2010.01
GLBTQ Archives, Central Connecticut State University
- Series II: Canon Clinton Jones Papers
  - HOMOPHILE MOVEMENT -- 1970'S, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
    3. Christopher Street Liberation Day Committee, 1971
    4. NACHO Bulletins
    5. One, flyers and letters
    6. Christopher Street Liberation Day Committee, 1972
    7. North American Conference of Homophile Organizations (NACHO)
    8. Gay Market Associates, Dr. John J. Soldo
    9. Wilcox, Steven W. "Gay liberation movement", paper May 9, 1972
  - HOMOPHILE MOVEMENT -- 1980'S Flyers, articles, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - "HOMOSEXUALITY: RESOURCES FOR REFLECTION" IN CHURCH & SOCIETY, May - June, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - HOMOSEXUALITY AND COUNSELING typescript of reviews of Canon Jones' Book, May - June, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - HOMOSEXUALITY TASKFORCE, Hartford, CT, May - June, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - HUMAN SEXUALITY UPDATE v.1 no. 1 Spring, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - HUTCHINSON, BILL "WHO, HOW, WHY? THE HOMOSEXUAL STORY", excerpted from center for Dialog, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - INSIDE "HOMOSEXUALITY" Supplement to the Trinity Tripod, Hartford, CT, Nov. 23, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - INSTITUTE OF HOMOPHILE STUDIES CATALOG Los Angeles, 1967 - 1968/1973 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - INTEGRITY - HARTFORD flyer, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - INTEGRITY NATIONAL Fact Sheet, May, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - JONES, CLINTON "PEDOPHILIA", January 26, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - JONES, CLINTON Articles about, biographical information, letters, interview with Frank Gagliardi, June 5, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - JONES, CLINTON, HOMOSEXUALITY & COUNSELING Typescript, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - JONES, CLINTON, HOMOSEXUALITY & COUNSELING Typescript (copy 2), undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - JONES, CLINTON, PASTORAL COUNSELOR AND THE MALE HOMOSEXUAL THESIS typescript, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - JONES, CLINTON, TERM PAPERS, 1967 - 1969 CREATION AND PROCESS, 1968 CIVILIZATION AND ITS DISCONTENTS, A RESPONSE, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - JONES, CLINTON, UNDERSTANDING GAY RELATIVES AND FRIENDS TYPESCRIPT, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - JONES, CLINTON, UNDERSTANDING GAY RELATIVES AND FRIENDS Typescript (copy 2), undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - JOURNAL OF GENDER STUDIES v.14. no. 1 WINTER SPRING/1992 v.14 no. 2 SUMMER - FALL, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - KALOS SOCIETY, HARTFORD CT. PROGRAMS, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - "LESBIAN AND GAY HISTORIES" SPECIAL ISSUE OF THE HISTORY OF SEXUALITY v. 4 no. 2, OCT. 1993 PT.1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "LESBIAN AND GAY ISSUES" IN CATALYST v.3 no. 4, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - LESTER, ELENORE, "GAYS IN THE SYNAGOGUE", IN PRESENT TENSE, AUTUMN 1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - LETTER TO A DIVINITY STUDENT, ABOUT TO BE ORDAINED, WHO IS DESIROUS OF ENGAGING IN A MINISTRY TO HOMOSEXUALS, May 23, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Lists of People/Organizations, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - LUCAS, DONALD L. HOMOSEXUAL AND THE CHURCH SAN FRANCISCO, MATTACHINE SOCIETY, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - MCNEILL, JOHN, "THE HOMOSEXUAL AND THE CHURCH" IN NATIONAL CATHOLIC REPORTER, October 5, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - MAGAZINE ARTICLES, 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    1. "How gay is gay, homosexuality in America" in Time v. 113 no. 17 April 23, 1979
    2. "Symposia in the flesh, An inside view of gay baths..." in Popular Psychology #6 May, 1973
    3. "Homosexuality and the Church, comment on two reports" in Christian Action Journal, Autumn, 1979
    4. "Playboy interview: Anita Bryant" in Playboy v. 25 no 5, May 1978
  - MAGAZINE ARTICLES, 1964-1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    1. "Forum talks to Anthony Grey" reprinted from Forum Magazine v. 2 no. 1, n.d.
    2. Dean, Heather "The varsity sports nobody reports" in the Gargoyle Magazine in Manorama, 1966?
    3. Berg, Roland, "the transsexuals, male or female? reprinted from Look, Jan. 27, 1970
    4. Hatterer, Lawrence J., "What makes a homosexual?" in Reader's Digest, Sept., 1971
    5. "Homosexuals in Revolt" in Life. Dec. 31, 1971
    6. "Homosexuals in management" in Industry Week, July 23, 1979
    7. "The homosexual, newly visible, newly understood" in Time, Oct. 31, 1969
    8. "Homosex: living the life" in Saturday Review, Feb., 1972
    9. "Tragic marriage" in Good Housekeeping, July 1968
    10 "The harsh facts of life in the gay world" in Maclean's, March 7, 1964
    11. Naylor, Gloria, "A message to Winston" in Essence, Nov. 1982
    12. White, Edmund, "Paradise found, gay men have discovered that there is friendship after sex" in Mother Jones, June, 1983
    13. "God and the homosexual" in Newsweek, Feb. 13, 1967
    14. Phillips, Gene D., "The homosexual revolution" in America, Nov. 14, 1970
    15. Rohr, Richard: "An appetite for wholeness" in Sojourners, Nov., 1982
    16. Star, Jack "The Presbyterian debate over sex" in Look Aug. 11, 1970
    17. Schott, Webster "Civil Rights and the homosexual" in N.Y. Times Magazine, Nov. 12, 1967
    18. "The Militant homosexual" in Newsweek Aug. 23, 1971
    19. "Maine's homosexuals speak out" in Maine Times July 28, 1972
    20. Crew, Louie "The gay academic unmasks" in Chronicle of Higher Education Feb. 23, 1974
  - MAGAZINE ARTICLES, 1977-1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    1. Crew, Louie "The church and the gays" in Christianity and Crisis, Feb. 4, 1980
    2. "Gays in the Church speak for themselves" in The Witness, Oct., 1977
    3. "Moment of Truth" in People May 31, 1993
    4. "Blitzing the AIDS virus" in People March 8, 1993
  - MAGAZINE ARTICLES, 1970-1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    1.Wright Elliott, "The Church and gay liberation" in Christian Century March 3, 1971
    2. Crucible, April-June 1980
    3. Jones, W. Paul, Homosexuality and marriage: Exploring on the theological edge" in Pastoral Psychology, Dec., 1970
    4. Finn, Robin, "The grim struggle of being gay" in Northeast Magazine Feb. 27, 1983
    5. Siegel Paul "Homophobia: Types Origins, Remedies" in Christianity and Crisis v. 39 no. 17. Nov. 12, 1979
    6. Kelsey, David "Homosexuality and the Church: theological issues" in Reflection, April, 1983
  - MAGAZINE ARTICLES, 1975-1981 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    1. Levine, Richard M. "How the gay lobby has changed" in TV Guide May 30 - June 5, 1981
    2. "Special issue on homosexuality" in Christianity and Crisis v. 39 no. 9 & 10 May 30 and June 13, 1977
    3. "Homosexuality and the church" in Journal of Current Social Issues v. 15 no. 1 Spring, 1978
    4. "Towards a theology of Gay Liberation" pamphlet in Movement no. 22, 1975?
  - MAGAZINE ARTICLES, 1964-1976 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    1. Pomeroy, Wardell, "Bisexuality" in Penthouse Forum March, 1976
    2. David, Lester, "Our son was different" in Good Housekeeping, Jan., 1965
    3. Hunt, Morton, "Sexual Behavior in the 1970s, Part VI: Deviant sexuality" in Playboy March, 1974
    4. Mead, Margaret, "Bisexuality: what's it all about" in Redbook, 1975
    5. "Gays and the law" in Newsweek Oct. 25, 1976
    6. "Gay America in transition" in Newsweek August 8, 1983
    7. Epstein, Joseph "Homo/Hetero: the struggle for sexual identity" in Harper's Magazine Sept., 1970
    8. "Homosexuality" in Sepia, Oct., 1964
    9. "Homosexuality" in Life June 26, 1964
    10. Star, Jack, "The homosexual couple" in Look, Jan. 26, 1971
    11. Lathbury, Vincent T., "Mothers and sons: an intimate discussion"
  - MALE CONCERNS SEX CONCERNS CHECKLIST (MALE) QUESTIONAIRE, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - METROPOLITAN COMMUNITY CHURCH, NEW YORK, CONNECTICUT, CHURCH BULLETINS, BY-LAWS, PRESS RELEASES, 1969 - 1974, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - METROPOLITAN COMMUNITY CHURCH, HARTFORD AN INTERIM POLICY, CELEBRATIONS OF RELATIONSHIPS, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - METROPOLITAN COMMUNITY CHURCH OF N.Y., PASTORAL LETTER, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - METROPOLITAN GUIDE SERVICES FOR LESBIANS AND GAYS, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - MINNERY, TOM, "HOMOSEXUALS CAN CHANGE" IN CHRISTIANITY TODAY, FEB. 6, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - MISCELLANEOUS, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - MOORE, JOHN V., "THE CHURCH AND HOMOSEXUALS, A PASTOR'S VIEW" Typescript, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - MORGAN, W.L.D. THE HOMOSEXUAL AND THE CHURCH: A HISTORICAL SURVEY, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - N.G.T.F. (NATIONAL GAY TASK FORCE) NEWSLETTER Flyer, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - NATIONAL COALITION OF GAY ACTIVISTS NEWS RELEASE, August 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - NORTH AMERICAN CONFERENCE OF HOMOPHILE ORGANIZATIONS (NACHO), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - NOUWEN, J. M. "HOMOSEXUALITY, PREJUDICE OR MENTAL ILLNESS?" REPRINTED FROM THE NATIONAL CATHOLIC REPORTER, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - N.G.T.F., GAY PARENT SUPPORT PACKET, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NATIONAL GAY TASK FORCE PACKET OF RESOLUTIONS ABOUT HOMOSEXUALS, NEWSLETTERS, 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NATIONAL MARCH ON WASHINGTON FOR LESBIAN & GAY RIGHTS OFFICIAL SOUVENIR PROGRAM, contains history of the gay rights movement, October 14, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NICHOLS, MARGARET, LESBIAN SEXUALITY ISSUES AND DEVELOPING THEORY Typescript, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NEWSPAPER ARTICLES, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - PAMPHLETS, 1956-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    1. This is a leaflet specifically about lesbians, Manchester, England 1985
    2. "I AM WHO I AM" in FORWARD Day by Day, Feb. March. April, 1980
    3. V. D. Information for Homosexuals New York
    4. Gay vote 1980 The National convention project
    5. Homosexuality Is... London, 1985
    6. Do you think you're Different? Alcoholics Anonymous, 1976
    7. INTEGRITY/HARTFORD
    8. THE HOMOSEXUAL ALCOHOLIC
    9. A Brief Guide to Alcoholics Anonymous, 1972
    10. "Heard any good fag jokes lately?" National Gay Task Force
    11. Southern California Council on Religion & the Homophile Bibliography, 1971?
    12. We are parents of gay persons, Hartford, 1983?
    13. A DIRECTORY OF RESOURCES FOR LESBIANS & GAY MEN, TRANSVESTITES TRANSSEXUALS, Hartford, 1985
    14. Safe Place For Those Grieving a Death by Suicide, Hartford
    15. THE CHURCH IN AN URBANIZED WORLD, 1964
    16. THE CHURCH AND THE HOMOSEXUAL, Conference program, 1970
    17. The Guild of St. Barnabas for Nurses News-Letter, Autumn 1956
    18. THE BEAUMONT SOCIETY "SOME QUESTIONS AND ANSWERS" England, 1983
    19. PARENTS OF GAYS, Washington D.C.
    20. A Response to the Report of the ... in the United States of America, August, 1979
    21. What Says the Church to the Homosexual Christian? May, 1969
    22. Religion and the Homophile, 1973
    23. Grey, Antony, "Christian Society and the Homosexual", reprinted from Faith and Freedom v. 19, no. 56 spring 1966
    24. Reaching Out, Through 1983, London, 1984
    25. Religion and the Homosexual, Spring 1967 26. Mental Health Lectures, Connecticut Mutual Life, 1966
    26. About Our Children, Parents and Friends of Gays, 1978
    27. Articles on homosexuality in The Saint Luke's Journal of Theology v.12 no. 3, June, 1979
    28. Articles on homosexuality in the Christian v. 4, no. 2, 1977
    29. Sexual intimacy in relationships, flyer, Yale continuing- education program in sex therapy, 1979
    30. "New ex-gay christian shores testimony" Church of the Good Shepherd, May 8, 1978
    31. When your rights are on the line, Gay Rights Advocates comes to defense 1979?
    32. Shepherd Carl W. "Hope for the homosexual" 1966
  - PAPER ON HUMAN SEXUALITY, A STUDY PAPER PREPARED FOR THE DIOCESE OF SOUTHERN OHIO, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - PARENTS OF GAYS AND LESBIANS, GAY PARENTS, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - PITTENGER, NORMAN "THE CHRISTIAN THEOLOGY OF SEX" Lecture typescript (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - POLITICAL PRIMER "20 QUESTIONS ABOUT HOMOSEXUALITY" PHOTOCOPY, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - PRESBYTERIAN LAYMAN "Task Force recommends ... that homosexuals be ordained...", February - March, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - PRIDE GUIDE '85 OFFICIAL GUIDE TO LESBIAN AND GAY PRIDE WEEK, June, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - PSYCHIATRIC K CLUB OF HARTFORD, Minutes, 1933-1956 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "QUESTIONS CHRISTIANS ASK ABOUT HUMAN SEXUALITY" IN ESA FORUM-6., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - RADER, DOTSON [REVIEW OF BOOKS ABOUT GAYS] IN N.Y. TIMES BOOK REVIEW, October 1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - RELIGION AND THE HOMOSEXUAL A SELECTION OF ARTICLES FROM ONE MAGAZINE, Spring 1967 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - RESOLUTIONS ON HOMOSEXUALS AND THE LAW, various groups and churches, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - ROSES, AUGUST, BAYSIDE, N.Y. THE LOURDES OF AMERICA, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - S. C. FORUM (SOCIAL CONCERNS) V. 1 NO. 1 "HOMOSEXUALITY AND THE CHURCH", October 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - SCARF, MAGGIE, "HE AND SHE! THE SEX HORMONES AND BEHAVIOR". N. Y. TIMES Magazine, May 8, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - SCHOTT, WEBSTER "CIVIL RIGHTS AND THE HOMOSEXUAL - A 4- MILLION MINORITY ASKS FOR EQUAL RIGHTS" N. Y. TIMES, November 12, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - SEX TOYS Catalog, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - "STONEWALL 69 GAY PRIDE 79 SOUVENIR PROGRAMME". LONDON, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - "TASK FORCE TO STUDY HOMOSEXUALITY", UNITED PRESBYTERIAN CHURCH, July, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - TRANSVESTISM, Articles, Pamphlets, 1977 - (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - "TRANSVESTISM. SOME QUESTION AND ANSWERS" London, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - TRUMBACH, RANDOLPH "LONDON'S SODOMITES..." IN JOURNAL OF SOCIAL HISTORY, Fall 1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - "UNDERSTANDING THE CLERGYMAN'S ROLE IN PASTORING THE HOMOSEXUAL", IN ST. LUKE'S JOURNAL OF THEOLOGY v. 10 no. 3, March 1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - UNITARIAN UNIVERSALIST ASSOCIATION, "ABOUT YOUR SEXUALITY", 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - UNITED CHURCH COALITION FOR LESBIAN/GAY CONCERNS "PASTORAL CARE PACKET", 1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - UNIVERSAL FELLOWSHIP OF METROPOLITAN COMMUNITY CHURCHES. 2ND ANNUAL GENERAL CONFERENCE, LOS ANGELES, September 3-5, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - UNIVERSAL FELLOWSHIP OF METROPOLITAN COMMUNITY CHURCHES. WASHINGTON FIELD OFFICE, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - NORTH AMERICAN CONFERENCE OF HOMOPHILE ORGANIZATIONS (NACHO), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - WELTGE, RALPH "HOMOSEXUALITY AS A CHRISTIAN ETHICAL PROBLEM" typescript (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - "WHAT ABOUT HOMOSEXUALITY?" IN SOCIAL PROGRESS, November/December, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - WHO MINISTERS TO GAYS? A GAY RABBI EXAMINES THE DILEMMAS AND DELIGHTS INHERENT IN MINISTERING TO LAYMEN... typescript, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - WOLF, RUTH "THE HOMOSEXUAL IN SEATTLE", undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - YORK, RICHARD H. AN OPEN LETTER TO THE CHURCH, typescript, March 25, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Filmstrips (5) in metal box series about your sexuality, Unitarian Universalist Association Male and female anatomy, Learning about sex, Breaking the language barrier, Love making, Homosexual lovemaking, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - OCTOBERFEST, INTEGRITY TABLE MATERIALS DISPLAY INFO., undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - PAMPHLETS & TAPES, 1970 - 1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Tapes
    1. Conference on human sexuality (2 tapes) HCCC. Inc
    2. 9th Int'l Symposium on gender dysphoria, Sept. 12-15, 1985
    3. National Public radio program 26, April, 26, 1977
    4. Friends for Lesbian & Gay concerns
    5. Mid-winter gathering, Feb. 19, 1984
    6. On being gay, cassette, 1973
    7. Ellis, Albert, [Tape] interview with John Jones
    Pamphlets
    1. "About coming out" National Gay Task Force, New York, 1978?
    2. "Answer to a parents' question about homosexuality," National Gay Task Force, New York, 1978?
    3. "Parents and Friends of gays" Washington, D.C.
    4. "Directory of Resourses for sexual minorities" Capitol Region Conference of Churches, Hartford, 1981
    5. "Homosexuality Counseling Specialists for Greater New England" Meriden, 1982?
    6. "Are you gay but not happy?" King's Ministries, Denver
    7. "Confide interview cassettes" (cassettes about transsexuals)
    8. "Parents of lesbians and gay men speak out", New York
    9. "Connecticut Gay Task Force, Why" flyer
    10. "What is Integrity?" Hartford
    11. "Phobe" flyer for book on sex change, 1970?
    12. Transsexualism Seminar May 1, 1974, flyer, Hartford
    13. "Kalos GLF", flyer
    14. "Our Right to Love" published flyer
    15. National Association of Lesbians and Gays "Join us in building Stonewall Park" Reno, Nev.
    16. Gerge W. Henry Foundation, Hartford "Understanding homosexuality"
    17. 7th intrnational gender dysphoria symposium, Lake Ta hoe, Nev. Program,March 4 - 8, 1981
    18. Integrity Gay Episcopalians and their friends "13 questions about"
    19. Hardesty, Nancy A., "God has no sexual preference..." publisher's flyer
  - WILKERSON, DAVID, A NEW LOOK AT HOMOSEXUALITY, LESBIANISM, MASTURBATION, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - WYRTZEN, JACK, LIBERATIING THE GAY PEOPLE, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Articles, 1940 - mid 1980s
    - ADOPTION (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - ADVOCATE MAGAZINE, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - AIDS, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - AMSTERDAM, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - ANN LANDERS, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ARMED FORCES, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - AUSTRALIA AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - BAPTIST CHURCH AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - BARS/RESORTS, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - BATHHOUSE, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - BISEXUALITY, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - BOOK REVIEWS, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - BRADLEY, DAN, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - BRYANT, ANITA, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - CAMPUSES, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - CANADA, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - CARTOONS, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - CATHOLIC CHURCH AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - CENTRAL CONNECTICUT STATE COLLEGE, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - CHURCH OF ENGLAND AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - CHURCH OF THE BELOVED DISCIPLE AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - CONNECTICUT'S GAY RIGHTS BILL, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - COUPLES, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - DEAR ABBY, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - DISCIPLES OF CHRIST AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - DRAG, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - EDITORIALS, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - EPISCOPAL CHURCH AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - FILM, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - GAY LIBERATION, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - GAY PRIDE, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - GAY TEENAGERS, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - GREAT BRITAIN, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - HARTFORD, CT, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - HOMOSEXUALITY, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - HOMOSEXUALITY, PREJUDICE OR MENTAL ILLNESS? BY HENRI J.M. NOUWEN NATIONAL CATHOLIC REPORTER, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - IN GOD WE TRUST (ORGANIZATION), undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - JAIL, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - JONES, CLINTON, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - KALOS SOCIETY, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - LANDERS, ANN, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - LAW, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - LUTHERAN CHURCH AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - MARRIAGES, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - MEDICAL, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - METHODIST CHURCH AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - MORMON CHURCH AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - MOVIES, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - NAVY, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - NORTHAMPTON, MA., undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - OBSCENITY, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - POLICE, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - POLITICS, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - PRESBYTERIAN CHURCH AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - PRISONS, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - PROJECT H, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - PROVINCETOWN, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - PSYCHOLOGY, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - QUAKERS AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - SALVATION ARMY, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - "SEX AS SPECTATOR SPORT IN TIME", July 11, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - SOCIOLOGY, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - SPORTS, undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - TEACHERS, undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - THEATER, undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - THERAPY, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - THOMAS, MARK IN "CONSENTING ADULT", undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - TRANSSEXUALISM, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - TRANSSEXUALS, undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - TRINITY COLLEGE, undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - UNITED CHURCH OF CHRIST AND GAYS, undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - UNIVERSAL FELLOWSHIP OF METROPOLITAN COMMUNITY CHURCHES, undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - VIOLENCE, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - "WHAT DOES IT MEAN TO BE A MAN?" BY SHERE HITE IN COURANT, Septmber 20, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - WHAT IT MEANS TO BE A HOMOSEXUAL BY MERLE MILLER, N.Y. TIMES, January 17, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Albany Trust, London Sex and Sense A Plan for Progress [Fund Raising Brochure], 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Alcohol: Correspondence, Flyers, brochures, 1979-1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Articles, 1969: "The Gay MECCA" by John Burks and Geoffrey Link Berkley Barb, v. 8, no 14, Issue, 190, Apr. 4-10, UH News Liberate Press: v. 1, no 17, Feb. 19, The Maze Article: Homosexual Behavior in Pre-Literate Societies: A Cross-Cultural Analysis and Application to American Culture by W. Donald Corydon, UH News, Feb. 19 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Baum, Gregory "Catholic Homosexuals", 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bibliography, Seventeen bibliographies on homosexuality, 1967-1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bibliography, 1971-1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bibliography on Transsexualism, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Bisexual: Behavior, Questionaire, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Book Bisexuality: Canon Jones' proposal for a book about Bisexuality, Correspondence, Chapters, Articles, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Brief History of the Gender Identity Clinic of New England [Hartford], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Church - U.S. Bishops, Principles to Guide Confessors in Questions of Homosexuality, undated/1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Coming Out in Hartford, In Northeast Magazine Courant, February 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Deborah Laganza Delivered from Lesbianism. Greatest is Love, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Episcopal Church. Standing Commission on Human Affairs and Health, Summary, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Gay Christian Workshop, Dayton, Ohio, [Application Form], June 16-20, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Gay Male Writing & Publishing. Ed. by Louie Crew, in Margins, May, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Gross, Alfred A. Articles, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - "The Hardy Boys Didn't Have Wet Dreams," by L. Flynn in Siecus Report, November 1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Help for the Homosexual, The George W. Henry Foundation, Hartford, CT, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Higgins, George C. Psychological Implications of Transsexuality, May, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Higgins, George C. Sexual Problems [Reprint], 1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Higgins, George C. & Randall G. Pearson, Some Psychological Considerations of Married Gender Disphoric Patients, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Homosexuality by Helmut Thielicke, Janus Society of America, [after 1961], undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Homosexuality, 25 Questions & Answers, Institute for the Study of Human Resources, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Homosexuality and Counseling: Correspondence with the publisher, Fortress Press, Book Reviews, letters to Canon Jones concerning his book, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Homosexuals and the Armed Forces, A Moral Dilema, Janus Society, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - House of Bishops Task Force on Homophiles and the Ministry [1 of 3], 1971-1976 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - House of Bishops Task Force on Homophiles and the Ministry [2 of 3], 1971-1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - House of Bishops Task Force on Homophiles and the Ministry [3 of 3], 1971-1976 (Box 7, Folder 29)